## HOANG HUYNH

☐ github.com/Hoang23 ♦ ♣ hoangh.com

4 0404551620 ♦ ► hoanghh9623@gmail.com ♦ ☑ Australian Citizen

Professional entry level technician with experience in the IT industry. Skilled in Active Directory, ticketing systems, documenting and knowledge bases with key strengths in communication and customer service

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Backend Developer Intern - Mentor Community

03/2020 - 07/2020

- Utilized boto3 SDK for AWS to create API endpoints to get user information, update user information and to search users based on location, company and profession from Dynamo Database
- Creating pull requests for features after testing Flask endpoints with Pytest and Postman

# Programming Mentor - Digimaker

02/2020 - 06/2020

• Lead group sessions teaching students computer science and coding concepts (data structures, conditionals, loops, functions, etc.) within Scratch, Python & Javascript

# Junior IT Analyst - Find Sports

12/2019 - 01/2020

• Worked closely with a team of software engineers to understand scraped products, then listing them on Catch to further expand the ecommerce offerings of Find Sports by 30% on the catch.com platform

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Scripting/Languages	Python, Javascript, SQL
Active Directory	Account creation, user and group management (IAM)
Operating Systems	Linux, Windows 10, Windows Servers - install, configure, troubleshoot
Cloud Computing	AWS - Account Management (IAM), EC2, S3, DynamoDB
General IT	Hardware assembly, DNS, Virtual Machines, cPanel, SMTP, SSH, Docker

#### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

Website Designer/Developer- Imperium Studios (imperiumgg.com)	01/2020 - Present
Analyst - Old Xavier Football Club	04/2019 - 09/2019
Front Desk Administrator Assistant - Reynard Street Neighbourhood House	11/2018 - 03/2020

### PERSONAL PROJECTS

Clear Tracker - Vue.js/FastAPI RESTful CRUD application to track jungle clear times %

- Implemented Javascript Axios API to make HTTP requests towards the FastAPI server that get, add, update and delete clears from the SQL database thus separating the server backend and client frontend
- Created frontend UI/logic using Vue.js features such as directives and components for the table, modal, upvote system etc

hoangh.com - Personal Blog/Portfolio website %

• Communicating data analysis and visualisation projects and exploring computer science concepts

### **EDUCATION**

Deakin University 2015 - 2018